const CARDS = [
  {
    front: "Georgia",
    back: "🇬🇪 საქართველო",
  },
  {
    front: "Georgian",
    back: "👩🏻 ქართველი",
  },
  {
    front: "Family",
    back: "👫 ოჯახი",
  },
  {
    front: "Coffee",
    back: "☕ ყავა",
  },
  {
    front: "Hot",
    back: "🥵 ცხელი",
  },
  {
    front: "Cold",
    back: "🥶 ცივი",
  },
  {
    front: "Goodbye",
    back: "👋 ნახვამდის",
  },
  {
    front: "I am sorry",
    back: "🌚 ბოდიში",
  },
  {
    front: "My name is",
    back: "💬 ჩემი სახელია",
  },
  {
    front: "I want",
    back: "👍 მინდა",
  },
  {
    front: "I don't want",
    back: "🙈 არ მინდა",
  },
  {
    front: "This",
    back: "☝️ ეს",
  },
];

export { CARDS };
